const Data = [
    {
        id: 1,
        title: "Git Merge",
        question: "What is the primary purpose of the `git` command `git merge`?",
        option: [
            {key: "A", value: "To create a new branch"},
            {key: "B", value: "To combine changes from two branches"},
            {key: "C", value: "To revert changes to a previous commit"},
            {key: "D", value: "To delete a branch"}
        ],        
        answer: "To combine changes from two branches"
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        option: [
            {key: "A", value: "Java"},
            {key: "B", value: "Python"},
            {key: "C", value: "C++"},
            {key: "D", value: "JavaScript"}
        ],
        question: "Which programming language is known for its write once, run anywhere philosophy?",
        title: "Programming Language",
        answer: "Java"
        
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        option: [
            {key: "A", value: "Windows"},
            {key: "B", value: "macOS"},
            {key: "C", value: "Linux"},
            {key: "D", value: "Chrome OS"}
        ],
        question: "What is the name of the popular open-source operating system created by Linus Torvalds?",
        title: "Operating System",
        answer: "Linux"
        
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        option: [
            {key: "A", value: "To host databases"},
            {key: "B", value: "To manage user authentication"},
            {key: "C", value: "To serve web pages to clients"},
            {key: "D", value: "To handle email communications"}
        ],
        question: "What is the primary function of a web server?",
        title: "Web Server",
        answer: "To serve web pages to clients"
        
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        option: [
            {key: "A", value: "Array"},
            {key: "B", value: "Linked List"},
            {key: "C", value: "Stack"},
            {key: "D", value: "Hash Table"}
        ],
        question: "Which data structure is known for its fast search, insertion, and deletion operations?",
        title: "Data Structure",
        answer: "Hash Table"
        
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        option: [
            {key: "A", value: "React"},
            {key: "B", value: "Angular"},
            {key: "C", value: "Vue.js"},
            {key: "D", value: "Ember.js"}
        ],
        question: "What is the name of the popular JavaScript framework for building user interfaces?",
        title: "JavaScript Framework",
        answer: "React"
        
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        option: [
            {key: "A", value: "Object-Oriented Programming (OOP)"},
            {key: "B", value: "Functional Programming (FP)"},
            {key: "C", value: "Imperative Programming (IP)"},
            {key: "D", value: "Declarative Programming (DP)"}
        ],
        question: "Which programming paradigm emphasizes reusable code and modular design?",
        title: "Programming Paradigm",
        answer: "Object-Oriented Programming (OOP)"
        
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        option: [
            {key: "A", value: "To create a new Docker image"},
            {key: "B", value: "To start a new Docker container"},
            {key: "C", value: "To stop a running Docker container"},
            {key: "D", value: "To delete a Docker image"}
        ],
        question: "What is the primary purpose of the docker command docker run?",
        title: "Docker",
        answer: "To start a new Docker container"
        
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        option: [
            {key: "A", value: "Amazon Web Services (AWS)"},
            {key: "B", value: "Microsoft Azure"},
            {key: "C", value: "Google Cloud Platform (GCP)"},
            {key: "D", value: "IBM Cloud"}
        ],
        question: "Which cloud computing platform is known for its scalability and flexibility?",
        title: "Cloud Computing",
        answer: "Amazon Web Services (AWS)"
        
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        option: [
            {key: "A", value: "Jest"},
            {key: "B", value: "No option"},
            {key: "C", value: "No option"},
            {key: "D", value: "No option"},
        ],
        question: "What is the name of the popular testing framework for JavaScript?",
        title: "Testing Framework",
        answer: "Jest"
    },

]

export default Data;